https://www.veloxmedia.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
Your privacy is important to us and our Privacy Policy outlines how we protect and respect the privacy of our clients and users that visit our website. This policy will cover how we collect and use the information you provide us for our services, advertising promotions, mailings and other services we provide. By using our services, website, and website tools you agree to the collection and use of the information you provide as outlined in our Privacy Policy.
Why we collect information
We collect information to provide you with the services that you request.
How we use and protect your information
VELOX Media uses the information you provide us in the following general ways: service provision, service improvement, contact, research and promotion.
VELOX Media will not share or sell your email address and other personal information with any third parties except our service providers. These service providers may have access to personal information needed to perform their functions but are not permitted to share or use such information for any other purpose.
Email Policy
If you provide VELOX Media with your email address, you may be contacted by VELOX Media for marketing and campaign update purposes. When you become a VELOX Media customer, you will be subscribed to our automated campaign update emails. If at any time you do not wish to receive e-mail from VELOX Media in the future, you may unsubscribe.
In order to unsubscribe from a mailing list, you may choose any of the following options:
Follow the unsubscribe link found at the bottom of the email you’ve received.
Contact your client success team or our customer service and ask to be unsubscribed from automated marketing and/or campaign update emails.
Remove yourself from VELOX Media’s automated campaign update emails by visiting our unsubscribe page. We will promptly update your preferences for this email address.
Please be aware that if you are a VELOX Media customer, a member of our client success team may continue to manually contact you via email for administrative or informational purposes, including follow-up messages regarding business transactions between VELOX Media and yourself. By law, such messages are not considered to be commercial e-mail.
How your data is stored and when it may be shared
We store your data in a secure database provided by third-party vendors and hosting partners that provided the necessary hardware, software and storage to provide you the services you request.
We take appropriate physical, electronic, and other security measures to help safeguard personal information from unauthorized access, alteration, or disclosure.
We may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with subpoenas, warrants, other valid legal processes. It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.
Use of Cookies & Other Technologies
VELOX Media uses cookies, tags, and other similar technologies. We use the information we collect to enhance your visit to VELOX Media and may be used to provide you promotional information regarding our services.
You may elect to refuse cookies. Please refer to your browser Help instructions to learn more about cookies and how you can opt out and delete these cookies.
Visiting our Website from Outside the United States
This Privacy Policy is intended to cover collection of information on our website from residents of the United States. If you are visiting our website from outside the United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection and other laws of the United States and other countries might not be as comprehensive as those in your country. Please be assured that we seek to take reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy is protected. By using our services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those service providers with whom we share it as described in this privacy policy.
Changes to Privacy Policy
We may make changes and updates to our Privacy Policy. We will post all changes on www.veloxmedia.com. We encourage you to review this policy frequently so that you are aware of any changes in how we collect and use the information you provide us. This policy was last updated November 2017.
Copyright 2005-2019
Enter your website URL and test
Get Your Free Instant SEO Audit Now!
Start the audit tool
Go to the top of the page
